[tires rumbling]
[engine rumbling]
3 YEARS AGO
[foreboding music playing]
[gravel crunching]
- [handbrake creaking]
- [music fades]
- [keys jangling]
- [lock rattling]
[door opens]
[soft tense music playing]
We're here. Get out.
Line up over here.
Move.
Keep moving.
Go.
Boss, I'll take these two.
- Hey!
- [henchman] Yes, sir.
Come on.
[grunts]
[in Burmese] Where are you taking
my sisters?
[worker in Thai] Stay still.
[in Burmese] That's my brother!
My brother!
[Seya] Let me go!
- [music intensifies]
- We came here together.
Seya!
[grunting]
[Seya] Nay Oo!
- [grunting]
- [Nay Oo and Nee An scream]
- [music concludes]
- [gunshot echoes]
[high-pitched ringing]
[Seya breathes shakily]
[soft tense music playing]
[Chai in Thai] Rern, how many
will you put on the boat?
[Rern] Ten.
[Chai] Take this piece of shit, too.
[Nay Oo sobs]
[sobbing]
[music intensifies]
[music falls]
[machinery whirring, clanking]
[Chai] Why is the catch
so small this time?
Maybe less than 50 tons.
How many are missing?
[worker] Two, boss.
[Chai] And you're just telling me now?
When PIPO comes to inspect,
what the hell am I supposed to say?
You better head back out right now. Go.
Or I'm docking all your pay.
[worker] Yes, boss.
- [workers shouting]
- [tense music continues]
[lighter clicks]
- [Seya grunts]
- [groans]
[music rises]
Where did you take my sister?
That cop.
He's working with you, isn't he?
Where is my sister?
Just calm down.
Which cop messed with you?
Tell me, I'll take care of it.
Stop lying.
You're all in this together, right? Huh?
Where did you take her?
Tell me or I'll shoot.
Your sister?
Probably been fed to the fish by now.
[music rises]
[gun safety clicks]
- [grunts]
- [Seya groans]
[groans]
- [Seya grunting]
- [music intensifies]
Think you're tough, bastard?
Think you're tough, huh?!
Don't even know how to take
the safety off, but you want to shoot me?
[indistinct chatter]
[worker] Hey, boss!
- [heavy thud]
- Boss! Boss!
- Boss, that's enough!
- [grunting]
The workers are staring.
[grumbles]
- [fast thud]
- Boss.
Call the commander.
[panting]
[worker] Hello, Commander?
A migrant tried to shoot Boss Chai.
Please send someone over.
- [panting]
- [music builds]
[music falls]
THE EVIL LAWYER
[music concludes]
[button clicks]
[Jittri] Is this the defendant's
X-ray film?
[Korn] Yes.
[Jittri] Is this the fractured collarbone?
[Korn] Yes, it is.
Can a patient with this kind of fracture
live a normal life after splinting?
[Korn] Yes, for the most part.
But they shouldn't move their arm much
or lift heavy things as it'd cause pain.
How about a month after the fracture?
Is it possible they could use a golf club
to bash someone's skull in?
In my opinion, it's impossible.
Typically, for an injury like this,
it takes two to three months to heal.
But it's only been a month.
Even if he raises his arm,
he wouldn't have the strength
to beat someone up anyway.
[Noi] Hold on.
[soft intriguing music playing]
Why didn't the defendant
mention this injury
during his initial statement?
The police never asked about any injuries.
But you called a doctor,
who was charged with rape, as your witness
and you were his lawyer for that case.
Isn't that a bit too coincidental?
I fear there might be collusion
to fabricate evidence after the fact.
[Jittri] Objection.
The prosecutor is bringing up another case
unrelated to this one.
[loud thud]
Prosecutor, keep your questions
relevant to the case.
- [exciting music playing]
- Don't just mix different cases together.
Or I'll have your back caned to a pulp.
- [gong clashing]
- Wangchao, Mahan!
[both] Yes, sir.
Bring forth the execution--
- Enough, you guys.
- [music stops]
It does seem too coincidental.
Won't the judge think we're colluding?
[Jittri] Maybe, but so what?
The court's duty is to consider this case.
They can't bring in other cases.
So you can relax.
Okay, sounds good.
[Nemo] Ouch, Mom!
[Kung speaking indistinctly]
[Korn] Don't slouch.
Or the bone won't heal right.
- Okay?
- Okay.
[indistinct chatter]
Your pain won't be for nothing.
[cell phone buzzing]
What is it, Ang?
THA KOH HOSPITAL
[Ang] The bullet didn't hit
any vital organs.
But Seya lost a lot of blood.
He was assaulted too.
So, the police let him rest
before the questioning.
The other side had filed a report first,
so Seya became the suspect.
Seya.
Listen to me, Seya.
The police will come back tomorrow
to ask you more questions.
But don't be afraid.
I'll be here with you.
[medical device beeping]
I should've shot him dead.
He fucking killed Nee An.
And he took Nay Oo, too.
[soft sorrowful music playing]
[sobs softly]
[Mek] Seya.
Let me ask you something.
Where did you get the gun?
[breathes shakily]
[insects trilling]
[reporter speaking distinctly over TV]
[music fades]
- [Noi] Jittri.
- Yes?
[Noi] Come here quickly!
Come here quickly, Jittri!
[reporter] …the scene
where a migrant worker
assaulted a local resident.
Our reporter went to the site to speak
with the injured victim
who owns the fishery.
- His name is Mr. Chaiwut Sinthornsuk.
- [foreboding music playing]
He stated he had never met
the attacker before
and suspected that
it was a case of mistaken identity.
His face has changed a lot,
but his eyes are exactly the same.
[reporter continues indistinctly]
[music rises, darkens]
[music builds]
[music stops]
[soft tense music playing]
[music intensifies]
- [music fades]
- [high-pitched ringing]
[muffled buzzing]
[cell phone buzzing]
[tense music resumes]
- Yeah?
- [Mek] I found the missing gun.
Nay Oo's brother used it
to shoot the fishery owner.
- I'm not sure if you saw the news.
- We'll talk later.
[dark daring music playing]
Hey, where are you going?
You can't go in there.
[Jittri] Mr. Chaiwut.
I'm Attorney Jittri.
I hear you're having legal trouble
that I can help with.
[machinery whirring, clanking]
[workers chattering]
The famous lawyer. I've seen you on TV.
But I don't have any problems.
I don't need a lawyer right now.
Ah, you have
a powerful backer helping you.
Why waste money hiring a lawyer?
But being too confident
isn't a good thing.
It will eventually backfire on you.
I'll just leave my card with you.
Just in case
you ever need my services one day.
[music fades]
[Jittri] That's a nasty scar.
What happened to you?
[soft tense music playing]
A dog bit me. Why do you ask?
You must have really pissed it off.
It bit you quite hard.
Contact me if you need help.
For you, I'll offer a special rate.
[music rises]
SERGEANT YUTTHACHAI KOMPACHARA
[Chanon] His old name was Yutthachai.
He left the force in '92.
- Right after the Ban Mae Tawo case.
- [music fades]
[Chanon] After that,
he completely vanished
and showed up again in 2013.
He's been running
the local fish markets ever since.
This guy's been with Anan
for a very long time.
Are you sure you can get him on our side?
A drowning man
will always do what it takes to survive.
The gun the boy used to shoot Chai
is Anan's, just like you said.
Here's the evidence and gun registration.
That was fast.
Will you tell me about yourself now?
Why the sudden interest in my life?
[Chanon chuckles]
[sighs]
EVIDENCE:
MIGRANT WORKER ASSAULTS EMPLOYER
Don't you want to know about me?
I already know everything I need.
[Chanon] I'm divorced now.
I told you…
that I'd show you just how serious I am.
My wife took the kid,
so I've given her the house.
This little guy is all I have left.
But it's fine. I get to start--
I made our boundaries very clear
from day one.
Do whatever you want with your life.
No need to tell me.
I've always been clear on my limits.
Is that enough? Or is it too little?
Only you can answer that.
Thanks for this.
[pensive music playing]
[inhales deeply]
[sighs]
[meows]
[chuckles softly]
[Kung] Have you posted
the gun details on Facebook?
[music fades]
How's it looking?
All done. I'm about to post it now.
HOW DID A POLICE GUN END UP
WITH A BURMESE WORKER?
Damn it! Are you writing a research paper?
Who's gonna share this crap, idiot?
Move. We'll handle this ourselves.
Hey, kid, is the setup ready?
- [electric buzz]
- [in English] Let's go, my brother!
[suspenseful music builds]
- [music stops]
- [echoing rumble]
[energetic electronic music playing]
Ready, set, and…
- [music stops]
- [computer chimes]
SCANDAL: TOP COP PLANTS GUN ON MIGRANT
[music resumes]
FISH MARKET BOSS ALMOST KILLED
[music stops]
[computer chirping]
NEED THE GUN OWNER'S NAME ASAP
[Kung] …go!
- [music resumes]
- [computer chiming rapidly]
100% POLICE WEAPON.
GUN LOVERS GROUP CONFIRMS.
DID THE COP HIRE THE MIGRANT?
CHECK THE REGISTRATION FOR OWNER.
[computer chirping, chiming]
SCANDAL OVER LEAKED WEAPON!
[Kung in Thai] Selling like hot cakes.
Pow!
Bam!
Boom!
[Kung] What a mess!
- [laughing]
- [computer chiming]
[Kung] We go all out, baby!
Absolutely no holds barred!
[group exclaiming]
GRABBING POPCORN.
TOP COP'S NAME DROPS TONIGHT!
[scanner whirring]
FIREARM LICENSE
FIREARM OWNER:
POL. GEN. ANAN METHANEEPAISAL
[Kung] Locked and loaded.
[in English] See you in hell,
my friend, bro!
- [echoing thud]
- [news theme music playing]
TRENDING NEWS
[in Thai] Hello.
I'm here with the top stories
for February 19, 2026.
The issue making waves
online right now
is an anonymous leak of evidence
showing the gun used in the crime
involving a migrant worker
attacking a fishery owner
in the Tha Koh Community.
According to the data and evidence,
the real owner of the gun
is Police General Anan Methaneepaisal,
also known as Big Anan.
- [foreboding music playing]
- Many are now asking,
how did Big Anan's gun end up
in the hands of a migrant worker?
Let's hear his response.
[reporter] The culprit used your gun
to shoot the fishery owner.
Did you know the owner's a former cop?
I don't think that's relevant to the case.
The only fact is that my gun
was stolen and used in a crime.
But the victim is Mr. Chaiwut Sinthornsuk.
Isn't he your former subordinate?
[sighs]
I've been a cop my whole life.
I've commanded countless officers.
I can't possibly remember all their names.
Excuse me.
- Sir!
- Sir, we need more explanation!
Please don't go yet, sir!
- [clock ticking]
- [reporter] Don't go! You need to explain!
- Sir! Sir!
- [muffled chatter]
Moving on to the migrant worker
who attacked the fishery owner,
our sources confirm that
the fishery owner, Chai,
or Mr. Chaiwut Sinthornsuk,
is a former subordinate of General Anan
- from his time stationed in Tak province.
- [dark pensive music playing]
[reporter] And the photo you see right now
is the one being shared online.
It shows that the two were close.
CRIMINAL CASE 1992
[clock ticking continues]
[music rises]
[music fades]
[machinery clunking, whirring]
[heavy clunk]
[worker] Boss! The cops are here!
[soft tense music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Chai] What's going on?
[officer 1] Search warrant.
I heard your boats have been
finding rare items lately.
I need to take a look around.
Who's your boss? I've never seen you.
I don't work for anyone.
Someone tipped us off,
so I came to search.
It's nothing personal.
[Chai] Who?
Who the fuck gave you the lead? Tell me!
My boats only carry fish.
There's no illegal shit here.
And if you don't find anything…
I'm coming for you.
[officer 2] Found it! It's crystal meth!
Lieutenant, come help me search.
Only carry fish?
Looks like we have a lot to discuss.
[officer 3] Excuse me.
[handcuffs jangling]
[handcuffs creak, click]
[cell phone buzzing]
[Anan sniffs]
[sighs]
[music fades]
[officer 1 scoffs]
[officer 1] Hey.
Who else will you call?
Tell me the truth.
Who's behind this?
How long have you run this fishery?
You answer me first.
Who put you up to this?
Where did the drugs come from,
and where are they going?
If you refuse to cooperate,
I'll have my guys search your house
and that might get your family in trouble.
[foreboding music playing]
Your daughter…
Maysa.
She's still so little.
I want a lawyer.
Mm.
[music fades]
We meet again sooner than I expected.
Who did you piss off
to get framed for drug trafficking?
But you picked the right lawyer.
Not many would risk their reputation
on a major drug trafficking suspect.
I've never had issues with anyone.
That doesn't mean
they don't have a problem with you.
There's massive money in fisheries.
If your market, one of the biggest,
suddenly went under,
everyone else would get a bigger cut.
Listen, if you want to beat this case,
do exactly as I say.
I'm listening.
[tense music playing]
Whoever set you up probably knows
the exact locations of your fleet.
Give me the coordinates of every ship.
And hide the illegal workers for now.
I'll handle the legal side.
[music fades]
And keep my wife and daughter out of this.
Even your big backer can't help?
[tense music resumes]
He's probably busy.
Are you sure you didn't do anything
to piss him off?
I've seen it too many times.
Powerful people are always
ready to discard little guys like us.
[music fades]
But don't worry.
I gave you my word. I'll do my best.
If little guys like us
don't help each other,
who will? Right?
[dark tense music playing]
[music builds]
[music concludes]
[officer 1] Whoa!
Look at the crazy cat lover.
- Oh.
- [music concludes]
Thanks so much, Ju.
- All set?
- [Jittri] Uh-huh.
- [Ju] See you later.
- See you, bro.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
How did it go?
He's starting to suspect Anan
planted the drugs to take him out.
I never thought your plan would work.
Turning people against each other is easy.
[sighs]
But I can't wait for you to turn me on.
Just drive.
[soft tense music playing]
- [insects trilling]
- [car horn honking]
[music fades]
[Rit] Mek.
What is it?
[sighs]
Can we talk?
I have something important to tell you.
- [Mek] Listen, today I--
- It's about Jittri.
[insects trilling]
I met her when she was a kid.
Not just Jittri, but her mother too.
Her mother once filed a complaint
stating that her husband
had been accused of human trafficking
and that he was later abducted.
[soft tense music playing]
[Rit]
The local police refused to file a case
because they feared the local bosses.
So she built the case herself…
and submitted it
to the Bangkok Criminal Court.
The chief forwarded it to me to review.
Why didn't you accept her case?
There was no evidence
for her claim about his abduction.
And looking at the police report,
it's highly possible that
her husband simply fled
to avoid arrest.
I wonder if Jittri still holds a grudge
about me dismissing her dad's case.
I might be overthinking it.
But you should stay on your guard.
Because we have no idea
what she really wants.
[tense music continues]
[brush scratching]
[cell phone buzzing]
- What is it?
- [man] Chai just got arrested, boss.
Arrested for what?
[man] They found meth in his cold storage.
Jittri was the one who bailed him out.
Huh…
- [knocking on door]
- [door opens]
Attorney Jittri is here to see you, sir.
[music rises]
[music concludes]
[Anan] Are you interested
in these things too?
They're interesting as an investment.
But not for worship.
I don't have faith in the abstract
or the intangible.
[chuckles softly]
You're a lawyer fighting for justice.
Isn't that an abstract concept too?
But I don't have faith in justice.
[chuckles] You don't…
because of your past?
If you mean our past, then perhaps.
But I came here to inform you
that I am now representing Mr. Chaiwut,
your close subordinate.
I'm sure you know he was arrested
for drug smuggling.
As a lawyer, I need to know
what other businesses
my client is involved in.
People can be terrifying when cornered.
- Those once loyal…
- [tense music playing]
…can just as easily betray you
in order to survive.
The coordinates of all your ships,
both registered and unregistered.
Ownership transfer documents.
Evidence of duplicate shipping licenses.
Forged work permits.
Fishing boats, fish markets… What else?
Human trafficking, how's that?
[music rises]
[Jittri] You have money,
strong backing, and influence.
But these days,
information is the ultimate weapon.
No one knows
when it might suddenly explode.
And the thing about an explosion
is that you can't control
who gets caught in the blast.
What do you want?
I don't really want anything.
I just want to help Mek beat his case.
Helping out a fellow human being
is the right thing to do, isn't it?
[sighs]
You must have wondered your whole life
about what happened to your father.
And the fact that you…
are defending the murderer
who killed my son…
[chuckles] …and threatening me
in my own home…
proves you just want answers
about your father.
[music turns ominous]
I'll give you some time to think it over.
But don't forget…
not every cop is loyal to you.
Last I heard,
someone is issuing search warrants
for all your ships.
But whether it actually comes to that…
is entirely up to you.
[music intensifies]
[music concludes]
[Jittri] We need to handle
Chai's drug case first.
He was caught red-handed.
If we want him to walk,
we have to spin a new story.
Wait, I don't get it. Why involve Chai?
The gun is already linked to Anan.
We need Chai to be our witness.
He knows everything
about Anan's operations.
He has proof that
Anan is trafficking humans.
The Burmese siblings
you're looking for do exist,
and they're Anan's victims.
I thought you said
you wouldn't go this route.
Things have changed.
We need to have a few options.
[Kung] How do we get Chai
off the hook, boss?
With a drug bust this big,
the DA has to indict him.
The sentence is prison either way.
But Chai won't be in jail.
This is Leh.
A Thai worker trafficked onto a boat
for several years.
He'll be the one going to jail
for this.
- [tense music playing]
- You'll use a scapegoat?
In a massive drug case like this,
the only way out is finding a fall guy.
I'm out then.
I'm fighting to avoid being a scapegoat.
And now you want me to frame this guy?
What kind of an asshole
would that make me?
[Jittri] You don't make
the decisions. I do.
- Are we done?
- [Mek] No, we're not.
Like hell we're done.
[Jittri] If we don't get Chai to testify,
we can't prove a third party
was involved in your case.
[Mek] And what makes you so sure
that Chai will agree to testify?
If Anan goes down for human trafficking,
he'll go down with him.
Right? You said it yourself
that Chai has always been
Anan's right-hand man.
I can drop his charges down
to just forced labor.
Chai is just a subordinate anyway.
The penalty for that is far lighter
than for drug trafficking.
Which do you think he'll choose?
Listen, Leh decided to do this.
He has his own reasons.
Don't worry about him.
He made his own decision.
And we'll compensate him as best we can.
[soft thud]
[Jittri] Let's continue, Noi.
[tense music continues]
[shredder whirring]
- [whirring stops]
- [cell phone buzzing]
- Hey.
- [music fades]
Daddy, when are you coming home?
Hmm… My sweet Maysa.
You're still awake, sweetie?
It's getting late.
Scold her, Daddy.
I told her to sleep but she won't listen.
She says she's waiting for you.
Don't wait up for me, sweetie.
Go ahead and get some sleep.
Hug Moo Daeng and give her a kiss for me.
I'll kiss you myself when I get home.
- Go to sleep, sweetie.
- [Maysa] Yes, Daddy.
[Chai] Mommy,
is the guard I sent still there?
Yeah, he's right outside the house.
Good. I'll hurry back.
[Kaewta] Maysa, say bye-bye to Daddy.
[in English] Bye, bye. Bye, bye.
[in Thai] Blow him a kiss.
Bye-bye. Mwah!
[cell phone beeps]
[Chai] Pui!
Get the truck ready. I'm heading out.
[thunder rumbling]
[engine rumbling]
[thunder rumbles]
Where the hell is everyone?
[thunder crashes]
[sinister music playing]
[Chai] Hey!
[groans]
[groaning]
[music intensifies]
[Chai groans]
[breathing heavily]
[groans]
[grunts, chokes]
[grunts]
[forklift whirring]
[chokes, groans]
[chain jangling]
[gasps, chokes]
[grunting]
- [choking]
- [music builds]
- [gunshot]
- [clank]
[gunshot]
- [music fades]
- [Chai groaning]
[Chai choking]
- [engine revving]
- [tires screeching]
[intense music playing]
[choking]
[forklift clanks]
[panting]
[groans, coughs]
- [chain jangling]
- [Chai wheezing]
[coughs]
[music falls]
Did you already know…
- that someone was coming to kill me?
- [music fades]
[Jittri] The person behind this
always meant to silence you.
I just sent my people to watch your back.
I know who did this.
I want this over as soon as possible.
You can handle it, right?
[Jittri] I can definitely handle it.
But I don't think
you're telling me the whole truth.
The guy who tried to take me out is Anan.
He might've planted the drugs on me
to keep me quiet about the gun.
You need to clear this case fast.
I'm taking my family out of the country.
What do you want?
Cash, gold? Just name it.
I don't want your money.
I'd rather hear the truth from you.
I'm already going to testify.
[Jittri] Not for this case.
The 1992 Ban Mae Tawo disappearance case.
What happened to the ferry driver?
[tense music playing]
That case is over 30 years old.
The statute of limitations has expired.
What more do you want from me?
What did you do to him?
[music rises]
[Chai] Argh!
[Chai screaming]
Let go of me, you little shit!
- Daddy!
- Muleng!
[in Shan] Go home!
- [young Jittri] Daddy!
- Go home!
- [Jai in Shan] Go!
- Go!
- [young Jittri in Thai] Daddy!
[music falls]
You're that little girl?
[music rises, darkens]
Your dad is dead.
What more do you want to know?
Why did you kill him?
I didn't do it.
Where did you put my father's body?
Get the drug charges against me
dropped first.
Then, I'll take you right to him.
[music intensifies]
[music concludes]
[Mek] Let's go over this again.
Where did the drugs come from?
[Leh] They came from the border by car.
Then they were kept in cold storage.
[Mek] Did anyone else know about this?
No one besides me and the users.
- [Mek] And the users on the boat…
- Only they and I knew about it.
The captain and Chai knew nothing.
[Mek] Okay.
- Let me ask you something.
- [Leh] Sure.
Why are you taking the fall for Chai?
Being on that damn boat… [clicks tongue]
It's awful. I'd rather go to prison.
[Mek] Is it really that bad on the boat?
My missing fingers… You know the winch?
The machine.
On the boat.
I had a long-sleeve shirt on,
and it got caught.
It pulled me in. I couldn't pull away.
So my fingers were torn off.
When I couldn't work without my fingers,
the skipper still forced me to.
He whipped my head with a stingray tail.
Then he poured boiling water on my back
and had the crew stomp on me.
All kinds of things happened on that boat.
They treated me like I wasn't human.
Like I was a piece of trash.
[brooding music playing]
[Leh] And I still don't even know
when my dad will get off that boat.
Your dad is on the boat too?
[Leh] Yes, he's still there.
When the skipper needed a scapegoat
my dad groveled at his feet,
begging him to pick me,
knowing I couldn't survive
on the boat any longer.
Missing fingers and unable to work.
Luckily, they didn't throw me overboard
to feed the fish.
I think that's enough for today.
[music fades]
[Leh] There's a lot
of messed-up shit there.
Shit happens every day.
The other day was super weird.
Out of nowhere, the skipper brought
a woman on board.
Guess he was just horny.
She was covered in bruises.
Walking with a limp too.
No idea how he could sleep with her.
- [chuckles]
- [soft tense music playing]
Was it this woman?
Hmm…
[music builds]
[music fades]
[intense music playing]
[Kung] Are you crazy?
Go to the Criminal Court. Ugh.
I have new information.
Leh told me that last week,
a woman was taken onto the boat.
So I showed him Nay Oo's picture.
He said they look very similar.
Most importantly, she's Burmese
and walked with a limp.
If it's really Nay Oo,
I'll alert the authorities to save her.
No. Stick to the plan.
And absolutely don't save her.
How do you know? He might be lying,
or he just got the wrong person.
But if it's possible,
shouldn't we at least try?
You're Chai's lawyer
because you want him to confirm
that Nay Oo exists, right?
If that woman is Nay Oo, it's all over.
We won't need Chai,
and Leh won't go to jail.
- And my case would close.
- And if it's not her?
[music fades]
There's nothing to lose.
We still save someone on the boat.
Leh's dad is there too.
[Jittri] How do you know
there's nothing to lose?
If you raid Anan's boat recklessly,
he'll catch on.
Then he'll pin the blame
on one of his men.
And Anan will get away with it.
[scoffs softly]
So in the end, this has nothing
to do with my case, right?
You just want to ruin Anan.
That's all you care about.
What happens to me in the end
isn't even your damn problem.
I know what Anan did to your parents.
[suspenseful music playing]
I mean, I get it if you want revenge.
But this is my life.
I'm not letting you use me as a pawn.
You think you're so much better than me
that you can judge me?
How long has that woman been gone?
Did you ever care
if she was dead or alive?
No! You never did!
You never really intended to help her.
You just want her to go to prison
so you can walk free.
If you say I used you as a pawn,
what about you?
How are you any different?
I'll bring that woman back
and I won't let her spend
a single day in jail.
So you'll see that we are nothing alike.
[music concludes]
[Ang] But be a little careful
with the white.
I don't want it to be 100% white.
I prefer off-white.
- [cell phone buzzing]
- Give me a second.
[tense music playing]
What's up?
[Mek] Hello, Ang. Listen.
I found a lead on Nay Oo.
Meet me at Chai's fishery right now.
- [engine revving]
- [music intensifies]
This island is the farthest we can go.
Past this point,
we enter Cambodian waters.
But from the info I have,
there's an island with a pier
just before crossing the border.
I just don't know which one.
Up ahead, there's an island
where local fishermen go to fish.
Then we better check them one by one.
- Okay.
- [officer] Got it.
Captain, let's check one by one.
- [Rern] Get up!
- [whip cracks]
[Rern] What? Are you dying?
I said, get up!
- Get up!
- [worker groans]
- [henchman 1] Skipper!
- Get up!
Skipper!
- The marine police are coming!
- [radio chirps]
[henchman 2] The police are moving in!
Lift the anchor and move!
[henchman 1] What do we do?
- Tell them to hide below deck. Hurry!
- [henchman 1 in Burmese] Hey!
- Get down!
- [Rern in Thai] I said, get up!
Get the hell up!
- I said, get up!
- [whip cracks]
[music builds]
- [music stops]
- [gun clicks]
- [gunshots]
- [worker groans]
Bastard!
Get below deck! Hurry up! Move it!
- Go!
- [intense music playing]
Get below deck!
- [man 1 in Burmese] Run!
- [in Thai] Move it! Get in there!
[intense music continues]
[officer 1] We've spotted the boat.
But no signs of life on board.
That's very unlikely.
[gunfire]
- [officer 1] Everybody get down!
- [Pang yelps]
- [music falls]
- [radio beeps]
Dispatch, Dispatch!
Requesting V.7 backup. Over.
I repeat, we are taking fire. Over.
[dispatcher] Reinforcements are en route.
- [radio beeps]
- Roger that. V.2, V.8.
[tense music playing]
Captain, ease us in slowly.
[gunfire continues]
- [clock ticking]
- [music intensifies]
[officer 1] Go, go, go, go!
Please wait right here.
[officer 2] Hey, freeze!
Drop your weapon!
- Drop your weapon!
- [officer 1] Drop it!
Slowly! Kneel down!
Check the top deck!
[officer 3] Top deck clear!
- Mek, wait!
- [Ang] Mek!
Mek!
Roger. Suspects are in custody. Over.
Roger that. V.2, V.8.
- Sir, you shouldn't go in there.
- Excuse me. Sorry.
[music fades]
[suspenseful music playing]
[music intensifies]
[Ang retches, coughs]
[music concludes]
[water dripping]
[boat creaking]
[dripping and creaking continue]
[waves crashing]
[water continues dripping]
[boat continues creaking]
[chains jangling]
[wind whistling]
[waves crashing]
[boat creaking]
[water burbling]